Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Closing of Lancaster Plant, Construction of Grand Island Plant, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
    By New Relations Department, New Holland Machine Company. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Political Activity and Political Assessments of Federal Officeholders and Employees, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By United States Civil Service Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Legislation in Western Europe on Mass Dismissals and Plant Closings, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By C & R Associates. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Economic Dislocation, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By Labor Union Study Tour Participants. Plant Closings, Plant Relocations and Plant Conversion. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Federal role in Economic Disloations, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By Thomas Kochan. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Union Response to Plant Cloings, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By AFL-CIO Human resources Development Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Exodus, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
    By Edard Kelly. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Political Attitudes of West Virginia AFL-CIO Union Members, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
    By Owen Tapper; James Neal. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Effects of Unionism o the Wage and Employment Levels of Police and Firefighters, Publication (Box 18, Folder 9)
    By Richard Victor. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Union Response to Plant Closings, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    By AFL-CIO Resources Development Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Training in New Short Supply Skills -- its possibilities and limitations --the Mansfield, Ohio Experience, Publication (Box 18, Folder 10)
    By Henry Fallerius. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Payroll Taxes and the Deficit, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
    By John Gebhart. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Financial Aspects of Industrial Pensions, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
    By Bryce Stewart. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial pensions or the Care of Faithful Workers, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
    By james Kavanagh. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industrial Pensions Report of Special Committee on Industrial Pensions, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
    By The Merchants' Association of New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Sage Philosophy of Pensions with a Review of Existing Pension Systems for Professional Groups, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
    By Henry Pritchett. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Selected List of References on Old-Age Security, Publication (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Works Council in Action, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    By Publication Department, Bournville. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers' Self-Management in Factories, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    By P. Romac; J. Franic. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Speech as Given, Publication (Box 18, Folder 12)
    By james Brinkerhoff. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Best Form of Collective Scale Contracts and Arbitration Agreements in the Printing Industry, Publication (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Childers Rosette Scheme, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
    By Action Society Trust. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Brent and Russel Face the future, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Brent and Russel Buy a Subsidiary, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: A New Product for Promex, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Childers Sort out the Mixers, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Reorganisation of Childers Sales Methods, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Promex Moves House, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: No Sale for Childers Dryers, Publication (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Managing for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
    By Henry Thole; Charles Gibbons. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Organization Structure and Dynamics, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
    By E. Wight Bakke; Chris Argyris. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Organization for Maximum Accomlishment, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
    By Milton Lightner. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Dissemination of Management Principles and Techniques, Publication (Box 18, Folder 15)
    By European Productivity Agency of the Organization for European Economic Cooperation. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Milton Plan, Publication (Box 18, Folder 16)
    By Alan Fox. An Exercise in Manpower Planning and the Transfer of Production. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How to Release Human Potential and Improve Productivity, Publication (Box 18, Folder 16)
    By Organization development Program Group. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Open shop Encyclopedia, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
    By Open Shop Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Closed Shop or the Open Shop - Which?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
    By Elbert Hubbard. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Open Shop "conspiracy", Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
    By John Edgerton. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Onward March of the Open Shop, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: How the Open Shop Brings Prosperity, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Why the Open Shop?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Bankers' Experience with over-65 Workers, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
    By Bankers Life and Casualty company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Future of Older Workers in America, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
    By Work in America Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Emerging Employment Optins for Older Workers: Practice and Potential, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
    By James Gollub. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Worker in an Aging Society, Publication (Box 18, Folder 18)
    By Institute of Gerontology, The University of Michigan. Item is in English.
- Box 18, Folder (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Older People Works and Retirement, Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
    By International Labour Office. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Older American, Publication (Box 18, Folder 19)
    By US President's Council on Aging. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The War and the Peace, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By The Labour Party. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: When Demobilization Day Comes, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: After the War - Full Employment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By Alvin Hansen. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Post - War Planning, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By National Resources Planning Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Post- War Agenda, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Post - War Planning, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: After the War - Towards Security, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: After Befense -- What?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The World of Tomorrow, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By Lectures in memory of Winthrop Ames. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Can we Avoid a Post Armament Depression?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By American Economic Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Discussions on the Postwar Outlook, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manuacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Guide for Post - War Planning, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Postwar Planning and Reconstruction, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By Seleted Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Report of the Commission on Post - War Training and Adjustment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By Institute of Adult Education. A Statement of Principles Relating to the Educaational Problems of Returning Solders, Sailors and displaced War Industry Workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Old World and the New Society, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of Participation in Contemporary Society, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Robert Miller; Fredrick Zeller. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Low-Income Life Styles, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Lola Irelan. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Politics of Poverty, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Michael Harrington. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Freedom Budget for All Americans, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By A. Philip Randolph Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Investment in Poor People, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Theodore Schultz. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Church and the Antipoverty Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Benjamin Louis Masse. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Underdeveloped Nation and the Underdeveloped Person, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By J. B. McKetterick. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Productivity and Poverty, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By Racine, Wis. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Resources on Academic Bargaining an Governance, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By Terrence Tice. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Tenure and Academic Freedom, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    By National Education Association of the United States. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Teachers' Oaths - Statutory Requirements and Oath Forms, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: collective Bargaining for Professional Employees, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    By American Chemical Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Business and the Professional Unions, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    By Worth Wade. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Faculty Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By Howard Means; Phillip Semas. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Faculty Organizing: Special Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By Bureau of national Affairs. Bulletin to Management. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Faculty Organizing: Special report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By Bureau of National Affairs. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Teachers' Oaths and Related State Requirements, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: N.S.P.E.'S Position on Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By The Engineer's Forum. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Why the Lag in Production?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By George Denny; James Lincon; Walter Reuther; Alfred Ward; Willard Shelton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Battle for Production, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Samuel Adams Darcy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: These are Your Weapons, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Howell White JR; Trevor Gardner. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labour Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By L. B. Whieldon. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Maximum Production: Warfare and Welfare, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: America's Factories, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: America Needs Unlimites Work Opportunity and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By C. E. Wilson. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Productivity and Unit Labor Cost in the Electric Light and Power Industry, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. 1917-1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Productivity andUnit Labor Cost in Selected Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Productivity and Unit Laor Cost in the Telephone and Telegraph Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistice. 1935-1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Productivity and Unit Labor Cost in Selected Mining Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. 1935 - 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Selected References on Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Productivity and Unit Labor Cost in Selected Manufacturing Countries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. 1919-1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: War Production in 1942, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Division of Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: What's Happening to Productivity?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Modern Industry. reprinted from Connecticut General Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Employment Service Record, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By United States Employment Service for Michigan. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Power, Machines, and Plenty, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Gloria Waldron; Frederic Dewhurst. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: report on the First Session: November 1948, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Anglo-American Council on Productivity. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: report os the Second Session: March-April 1949, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Trade Unions and Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By William Chartener. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Selected references on Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Hellen Reville as supervised by Hiram S. Davis. 1939 - 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Uses of Productivity Data in American Manufacturing Establishments, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: The Productivity Measurement Program of the Bureau of Labor Statistics, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Measurement of the Effectiveness of the Productive Unit, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    By Edward Smith; R. Beeching. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Legislative History of the Davis-Bacon Act, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    By Division of Wage Determinations, Office of the Solicitor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Davis - Bacon Act: It Works to Build America, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    By The Building and Construction Trades Department, AFL - CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The War on Wage Protection: The Business Offensive, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    By Center to Protect Worker's Rights. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Davis-Bacon Act The Economics of Prevailing Wage Laws, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    By John Gould. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Davis-Bacon Act Selected References, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Economic Systems, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By Harold Moulton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How Can a Better Understanding of our Economic System be Fostered?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By Charles Taft; Frank Abrams; Everett Needham. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Outlook for Private Enterprise in America, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Substance of the Enterprise, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By James Adams. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Fallacies About out Private Enterprise System, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By National Association on Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Free Enterprise for Whom?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By Emil Rieve. A Labor view of the American Economy and its Collective Bargaining Problems. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Re-Privatizing Public Enterprise, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By Chamber of commerce of the United States. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Total Security - A Challenge, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    By Charles Wilson. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Industrial relations or Twenty Years of Co-operation Between Capital and Labor, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By John Baker. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Profit-Sharing and Co-Partneship, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Ernest Mundy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Joslyn Plan, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Marcellu Joslyn. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Fallacy of Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Norman Fregger. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Sharing Profits in Industry, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Thomas Ford. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Story of Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Council of Profit Sharing Industries. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: 50-50 Profit - Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By The National Cash Register Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Profit Sharing - An Adaptable Group Incentive Program, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By B. L Metzger. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Profit Sharing Background, Current Developments, Future, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By J. J. Jehring. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Selected List of References on Profit Sharing and Bonus Systems, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Grace Hadley Fuller. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Its Principles and Purpose, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By American Profit Sharing institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Will Profit Sharing Increase Employment?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By The Pro & Con Monthly. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Profit Sharing for the Wage Earner, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Profit Sharing in Industrial Establishments, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Sharing Profits with Employees, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Report on Profit-Sharing and Labour Co-partnership in the United Kingdom, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    By Intelligence and Statistics Department. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Productivity: The Link to Economic and Social Progress, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
    By Curtis Prendergast. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Shating the Benefits of Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By Mark Roerts. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Productivity in Stae and Local Government, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By The Wingspread Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: So, Mr. Mayor, You Want to Improve Productivity.., Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By National Commission on Productivity. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Opportunities in Improving Productivity in Police Services, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Productivity and Automation, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By Henryka Cwalek; William Dunwiddie; Omar Kussow. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Productivity A measure of Economic Progress, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour for Selected Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By W. Willard Wirtz. 1939 and 1947-61. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Indexes of Putput per Man-Hour for Selected Induatries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By Arthur J. Goldberg. 1939 and 1947-60. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Indexes of Output per Man-Hour Selected Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    By W. Willard Wirtz. 1963 and 1947-62. Item is in English.
- Box 19, Folder (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employee Understanding and Teamwork for Greater Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By John Troxell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Productivity and Policy Decisions, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Richard Beaumont. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Railroad Transportation Industry, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Maurice Tobin; Ewan Clague. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Productivity Increases Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Selected Reference on Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Bureau of Labor Statistics. September 1945 -- September 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Productivity, Earnings, Costs and Prices in the Private Nonagricultural Sector of the Economy, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: The Collective Bargaining relationship in the United States and its Relationship to Productivity and Technological Change, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Otis Brubaker. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Sharing in Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Ted Silvey. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Better Defense or Better Living or Both, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Progress in Productivity and pay, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Eddy-Rucker-Nickels Company. A Continuing research Report based on the official U. S. Census of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Our Miracle of Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Economic Research Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Productivity -- What it is and How it is Measured, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Peter Steiner; William Goldner. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Productivity and Prices and Wages, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Jean Fourastie. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Productivity and Economic Progress, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Frederick Mills. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Union's Role in Helping Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Joseph Beirne. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Practical Methods of Increasing Productivity in Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: The Unions and Productivity, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By Willfried Schaefer. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Law of Production, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By The American Economic Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Productivity Gauge of Economic Performance, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    By National Asociation of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
- Box 20, Folder (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: So You Dont Ride the Trains Any More?, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Harold Martin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Text and Analysis of Work Rule Demands of United States Railroads, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Facts vs Fallacies on Railroad Bargaining, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Railroad Transportation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Bureau of Railway Economics. 1911-1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Railroad Transport, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Bureau of Railway Economics. A Statistical Record, 1921-1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: 50 Years of Railroad Signaling, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Quiz on Railroads and Railroading, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Quiz on Railroads and Railroading, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Associaation of American Railroads. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Job Protection, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Due Process on the Railroads, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Joseph Lazar. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Maintenance of Way Employment on U. S. Railroads, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Willliam Haber; John Carroll; Mart Kahn; Merton Peck. Item is in English.